eteachergroup.com 2015-05-20

# eTeacher Privacy Policy | Learn a foreign language

This document contains information regarding our privacy policy and practice and is brought to you so you feel comfortable using our website and services. It is presented for your benefit and describes how we collect and use information. Please take a minute to read the following statement in order to make sure you agree with our practices. By using eTeacher.com and / or its web properties, you permit the usage of your Personal Information (as such term is defined below) as outlined below in our Privacy Policy and in the Terms of Use.

 **Collection of Information**

eTeacher highly respects your privacy and takes special measures to insure that any personal information collected by us is used solely in accordance with our privacy policy. It is important for us that you understand both what kind of information is collected and how it is used.

As part of the services granted by this website, people using eTeacher.com may leave their private details on our registration form. We will not share this information with any non-affiliated third parties unless you specify otherwise.

 **Type of Information Collected**

At the outset of joining the services provided in this website, you may be prompted to provide certain contact information, in order for us to be able to identify and/or contact you regarding our services and/or products. Such prompted information may include any of your first and last name, mailing address, e-mail address, Instant Messenger ID, and certain location information such as city, state, and/or zip code, as well as other necessary contact related information ("Personal Information"). Kindly note that Personal Information may also include certain information which is not explicitly submitted by you, as we log your browser-type related information, IP address, requested URL, referring URL, and timestamp.

 **Use of Personal Information**

eTeacher will not sell, provide, rent, trade, or otherwise share your Personal Information with or to third parties for their promotional use, except from eTeacher’s business partners. Please note however that we may use your email address to send you updates or news regarding our activities, but you may choose not to receive emails of this type by clicking on the "Remove me from mailing list" button located on the bottom of our emails.

Please be further advised that certain browser-type related information, IP address, requested URL, referring URL, and timestamp data may be used by us to diagnose our service, monitor our servers and make sure we provide you with the highest quality of service. In addition, we may use this information to perform statistical analyses of the behavior and characteristics of people using the service in order to measure interest in and use of the various areas of the site and to inform advertisers of such information as well as the number of people that have been exposed to or clicked on, their advertising banners, who, in turn, may also serve content and/or advertisements and collect information directly from you.

 **Security of Information**

As we are committed to protecting the security of your Personal Information eTeacher uses various security technologies and means in order to help protect your Personal Information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure.

 **Cookies**

Upon your first visit to eTeacher.com, a cookie is sent to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. A "cookie" is a small file containing a string of characters that is sent to your computer when you visit a website. Cookies cause no harm to your computer or to your web browsing experience; on the contrary, we use cookies to improve the quality of our service and to better understand how people interact with us. Please also note that our advertisers may also place or recognize cookies on your browsers.

Although most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent, and you can also easily remove any cookie sent to you from our website.

 **Links to Other Websites**

This website may contain links to third party websites. eTeacher is not responsible for the privacy practices of these websites, nor will eTeacher be liable for any content related claim arising from visiting such third party websites.

 **Changes to Privacy Policy**

eTeacher may from time to time update this privacy policy. When we make these updates, the "last updated" date listed at the top of this policy will be changed accordingly. If a material change will be made in this statement, which affects your rights, eTeacher will notify people using the service by placing a more prominent notice on our home page.

 **Privacy-Related Inquiries and Complaints**

If you believe that eTeacher has not complied with this privacy policy with respect to your Personal Information or if you have other related inquiries or concerns, please feel free to write us at [privacy@eTeacherGroup.com](mailto:privacy@eTeacherGroup.com).

 **Governing Law**

This privacy policy shall be governed by and interpreted in accordance with the laws of the State of Israel, without giving effect to its conflict of laws provisions, and any action arising from or related to this privacy policy and the use of our Web Site shall be brought only before the courts of Tel Aviv, Israel.

Copyright

All rights reserved. © 2011

eTeacher
